Translated by the community of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
We will make a check call every six hours.
Third unanswered call.
We have not heard from the professor for 18 hours.
The Professor will be solving some pending issues.
- We are in a critical situation. - No, we'll be in a critical situation,
if the Professor does not call within 6 hours.
In this case we will activate the Chernobyl plan.
I want you to find all the estates ...
within a radius of 100 kilometers from the pharmacy of Palomeque.
If they bought the medicines there, it means that they were close by.
Inspector, we found the property.
You have to scour every single corner of this house.
All the plan, fuck. Hours, photos, programs.
It makes no sense.
- Call Alberto. - Your ex-husband?
Is not it the best of the scientific? So, come on.
- Hi, Raquel. - He is Salva, my current companion.
- Salvador Martín, pleasure. - My pleasure.
All this stuff is worthless.
Ángel has arrived farther than you with the footprints he has found.
Which footprints?
He had recovered a personal object, a teaspoon.
Ángel picked up some of the gang or otherwise went near.
They stopped the Professor.
They are questioning him at the door of the house in Toledo.
They have the professor.
There will be no tunnel to the hangar because we will find GEOs waiting for us.
- Which of you still believe in the Professor? - I believe in the Professor.
- Rio? - I believe what I see.
- Moscow? - I keep counting on the Professor.
I vote to leave here, right away.
I have good reasons to be on the side of the Professor.
I'm on the side of Berlin.
Are you sure you want to do it?
He was your father.
It is the only thing that matters.
We will do it for him.
If there's something useful here, I know where it is.
All they wanted to eliminate seriously ...
they will have burned him in here.
It's the safest way to destroy something ...
that's what we all would do.
- Raquel, I do not want to disturb, but ... - I bring this to the central Canillas.
I really had to go to Madrid, I would have taken the bus.
- Am I a bit 'upside down? - Do you want me to stop?
If you do not mind, I would be grateful.
I was thinking back to what you said before ...
to the fact that you wish the best of Raquel.
If so, you do not ...
he discovered his sister.
- Piece of shit. - Get out of the car.
You are under arrest for assault on a public official.
Listen to me.
I have to ask you a favor...
when the mess breaks up, you'll have to deliver.
- Rio. - When things get complicated ...
I'll be by your side ...
what happens happens.
Give me the revolver.
Tell us about the Chernobyl plan.
I'm the only one in here who knows the plan.
You will not have the slightest idea how to get out of this fucking trap.
What do you want to do with me?
Son of a bitch, I hate you.
Why must it be the end of something?
It could not be the beginning ...
of a wonderful friendship?
No!
Beware, it looks like a hostage. We await orders.
We are approaching.
He looks like one of the robbers.
Got it.
Who is it? I do not see the face.
It's Oliveira, sir.
We took it, sir.
Why the fuck did they deliver one of theirs?
Keep yourself at 20 meters, you may have explosives on.
- To the ground! Safety distances! - Anti-bomb protocol.
I repeat, anti-bomb protocol. It could be a trap.
To the ground! To the ground! Safety distance, possible explosion!
Get the suit off.
Listen, take off boots and overalls.
Remove boots and overalls!
Fast!
Take off your boots and your suit, fast!
T-shirt, raise your shirt!
Ammanettatela.
On the ground, on your knees!
Hands up.
Raise those hands.
Do not shoot, I repeat, do not shoot.
That nobody touches that woman, I want her alive.
Tokyo.
Tokyo!
Stop.
Stop!
Fuck.
There are three types of risks: Killing you, hurting you ...
or who will take you. Today we will talk about the third.
Tokio?
Do you have any idea what to do if they catch you?
A kick to the balls?
You must always ...
keep in mind the leitmotiv of this shot ...
to take...
in time
Take time.
In reality...
you must exploit all the possibilities you have to succeed.
The stomach.
- Here we go. - I can not breathe.
You broke something, fuck me.
Sir, the inmate says she feels a strong pain.
He says he can not breathe. I request medical assistance.
Okay, have it checked by a doctor.
Got it.
Come on.
- It hurts. - Careful.
It hurts, it hurts so much.
- A little further back. Back. - Fuck.
You lied to us.
Did you say "no personal relationships" and Berlin is calling you by name?
Sergio?
Why is that what you call, right?
Tokyo, maybe tomorrow, with a fresh mind, we'll see things ...
Tomorrow I will not see anything.
I accepted to participate because I trusted you ...
because you would have been our guardian angel.
Guardian angels do not lie.
My name is Sergio.
Sergio Marquina.
My father was a robber.
They killed him during a shootout ...
with the police, at the entrance of a bank, it had been him ...
to design the shot.
Tokyo, between ...
among all those in the band, you're the one with the warmest head.
The time will come when you will think that everything is about to collapse.
That everything is going wrong.
That you are completely alone.
But I promise you it will not go that way.
I thought of everything.
And then, I'm a lucky man.
Are you a lucky guy?
Tokyo, I will not abandon you.
You must never forget it.
The worst things that can happen to you when you're in charge of a robbery are: First:
to be arrested for assaulting the inspector's ex in charge.
Take the fingerprints and put it inside.
Second: they ask you for the identity card ...
- Documents. - And you can not give it a fake one.
Third: they take your fingerprints.
And if more than coincide with those found in a steering wheel ...
on which they are investigating ...
- even worse. - Empty the pockets in that pan.
Fourth: take your belongings ...
especially if you have the keys to the hangar ...
in which there are the control center and the exit of the escape route of the thieves ...
and a bottle of poison.
It is a medicine for a heart condition ...
it's called Digoxina.
With which a few hours before you wanted to kill the mother of the inspector.
Follow me.
Stay here waiting to be heard.
Rafa.
From the mint: A few minutes ago the kidnappers have literally thrown out ...
using a stretcher, a person bound and gagged ...
which was recovered by the agents of the special intervention team.
This is Silene Oliveira, one of the kidnappers inside the Mint ...
LAST IMAGES LIVE FROM THE STATE OF THE STATE
and who is currently undergoing a medical examination ...
in the infirmary of the security zone.
Fifth: that your accomplices lose their reason.
La casa de papel - 1x11 The cabeza of the plan
MONDAY, HOURS 19
81 HOURS FROM THE BEGINNING OF THE RAPINA
Tokyo lost his mind.
He did not resist.
It was not easy.
But I had no choice but to deliver it.
Take hands.
I beg you...
we are here risking our lives ...
it does not cost so much to take each other's hands.
When you open a wound ...
the plates are compacted ...
to close it.
If they do not, the body inevitably dies.
A wound has opened and we must compact ourselves.
- Why the hell do you talk about platelets? - Rio.
What would you be?
A preacher?
The leader of a sect?
Will you ascend in space with him holding hands?
- Rio, you have to calm down. Immediately. - No. No, I do not calm down.
You sent Tokio to jail.
Do not you dare ask me to calm down, fuck ...
She's my girlfriend.
Girlfriend.
And you ruined her life.
It's your first love.
It's the end of summer and you have to say goodbye to Susan on the French Riviera ...
- It seems the end of the world, but it is not. - Close that fucking mouth,
psychopath of shit ...
that you do not have a fucking idea of ​​what you say, clear?
Is there anyone who's not crazy, here?
Moscow.
Do you agree with the end of Tokyo?
Son ...
he lost his mind.
We have all seen it.
Nairobi.
We have rules ...
we voted ...
she did not accept it ...
and then he was crazy.
Denver.
You realize how stupid she is, do not you?
Of course I understand that.
But he played Russian roulette with Berlin ...
how do you think?
- Nothing happened, fuck. - But there's not a hair.
Fuck.
little boy, open your eyes.
In Tokyo he gave her the brains and we can not keep a bomb.
Unbelievable ...
you are all with Berlin ...
- with a shit psychopath! - No, we're not all with Berlin ...
- we are all with the Professor. - With the Professor?
They arrested him.
We have all seen it on television.
He will not call ...
he will not wait for us at the exit of the tunnel.
Now you will say that there are two hours to the control call, right?
Wonderful.
Because it's the last one.
Let's see what the hell you'll do when he does not call.
I do not intend to stay here to see it.
Some hostages have gone ...
Tokio left ...
I guess it's not a problem if I leave too, right?
You know it's not true, Rio.
But it's your decision and we respect it. Come on.
Stay there.
Someone comes to close the front door, right?
Wait!
Just come out ...
take this and raise it ...
because they understand that you go out in peace.
There are shooters, I do not want anything to happen to you. Come on, take it.
Hug me.
I wish you the best.
Never stop believing in love ...
it's important.
Trust me, trust me ...
trust me.
You have to free your mind so you can think lucidly.
Trust me ...
do it, let yourself go.
Let yourself go, so ...
what's this.
A little 'rest and will come back to itself.
Killing Berlin.
Killing Berlin. Killing Berlin. Killing Berlin. Killing Berlin.
Kill. Killing Berlin. Killing Berlin.
Killing Berlin.
This was the only phrase that resounded in my head ...
but there was no way ...
as far as I thought ...
I could not find a way to crush Berlin's life ...
without even going to Rio.
I could reveal the escape plan ...
the position of the hangar ...
but a similar revenge would also be twisted against Rio ...
my little Rio.
And I remembered how much I had struggled for my love to be there.
Well, I would say that today's lesson can end here.
What a hunger. You no?
Rio ...
remember I told you we had to install a program?
Alone.
The moment has come.
Fuck.
Nice single room, Professor ...
Is that where you bring the girls?
Let's get to work that there's a long way to go.
Fuck, Professor, who made this mess?
A company.
Of course, a company, like no.
It looks like a cousin handyman job.
Okay, I did it with tutorials found on the internet.
Beautiful shit tutorials.
That's why you are there, right?
There.
the voice editing program is ready.
To simply talk to the police ...
press MS. To contact the museum, zero.
That's all, the change of the voice ...
the program does it directly when you speak.
- I can try it? - Self.
Talk to the robber.
- Can you remove the woman's voice? - Sorry.
Whore. Asshole. Frocio.
Okay, I'll stop.
Try now.
Talk to the robber on the command ...
That's fine.
Now we have to log into the illegal internet network ...
- to buy illegal things. - In the deep web?
The submerged web.
Can you explain to me what we are doing?
I deactivated defenses and wi-fi and we connect via ethernet.
And I diverted the data traffic through a VPN via the Tor network.
Sorry then...
CONTINUE
done!
There's everything, rifles, grenades, rocket launchers ...
it's like the USSR arsenal outlet. Look, a tank.
We could enter the mint with a tank like the A-Team,
- with the rifles, the plastic explosive. - Do you know what a Browning is?
Yes, sure!
Well, we buy a Browning machine gun, assault rifles, guns and ammunition.
A V-750 missile, fuck! It's a cannonade.
Imagine breaking into this with the tick, open the door and ... bam!
Missile V-750 aimed directly at the cops and ... boom!
Everyone fuck off. It would be great, fuck.
It's not expensive either, 60 bitcoins.
Equivalent plus or minus € 150,000.
It's a good price.
Why did you exclude Rio from the plan?
So,
I do not owe you an explanation, but ...
I believe it is not ready.
You are wrong.
Are you sure?
Work with him for months ...
you know him and you know he's deeply ...
immature, it is not aware of what we are about to do.
The bullets out there are real, there are no more lives like in video games.
- He knows what he does well. - Listen to me, responsibility is mine ...
I do not mean to involve a kid.
I'll give him a part for the trouble, but he's out of the plan.
Rio is the best in his field and you know it.
That's why you chose it.
It's a brains fucking ...
and you know that genes are weird.
Do you think you are an example of maturity?
- Tell me.
Do you consider yourself a normal person?
Do you think it is normal to order shirts by color?
Did you see yourself?
Who buys your clothes?
Your aunt, Sister Gertrude?
And those?
- What are? - Of origami ...
- It's a millennial technique, please ... - What is it?
Are you afraid that the paper dolls will break you?
Welcome to Jurassic Park.
Help me, a dinosaur wants to eat me!
What's the difference ...
between this ...
and play video games?
I'm sorry, but it's not a decision that's up to you to take.
If instead...
if Rio goes away, do not count on me.
Because I'm not mature enough either.
Well...
maybe each of us is a little immature, in his own way.
- And that makes us all a bit ... - Specials.
.
And maybe it's not bad.
Maybe it's a virtue.
It is possible
Sure.
But do not tell me ...
tell him, he's behind the door.
Thank you very much, Professor.
You will not regret it, I promise you.
Thank you.
Are you the one who beats the cops?
Well, now I'll read the penal code.
Article 33
offense of aggression to a public official.
Penis from one to four years of imprisonment.
And we will do our best to spend four years in a cool place.
Could I please talk to my lawyer?
Sure.
Speak to us as well.
You will need it.
I need the phone, the number is saved.
They took it with my personal belongings.
Wait here and do not move.
I'm sorry for the girl ...
because among those bastards of the cops ...
and they ...
I prefer the kidnappers.
They made a bang.
Well, let's see how it ends.
I tell you...
with all the riddled riders.
Fuck.
Sons of a bitch.
Sons of a bitch. Fuck.
Look, look, Mr. Prieto.
Miss Tokio.
Do you often interrogate women in underwear?
Why did they deliver it?
Well!
Shit happens.
Why did they hunt her tied to a stretcher?
I had some fuss ...
with whom he commanded.
I tortured him for a while and did not take it very well.
Already.
You must know that your money will always be ...
Insured parties:
How I contacted you at the beginning ...
I would also contact you once you got out of prison to give it to you.
Therefore the plan remains valid ...
because at worst,
after a couple of years, you will have your money. And in the best ...
I'll try to get you out of jail when the waters ...
- they will have calmed down. - That the plan is still valid means ...
that you do not have to talk to the police,
nor with the judge ...
- nor with other prisoners, no? - Exactly.
I'd rather bite my tongue, chew it and swallow it,
rather than talking.
Well, I'd say it's a method ...
effective, a bit extreme, but effective. I wanted to offer you something a little more ...
Fair]
An interrogation is like a game of skill,
how to fly a kite. It can precipitate at any moment.
With the right hand ...
you leave little by little ...
Ed. Il Filo
of truth.
How many people are you in there?
Eight.
The same eight who organized the shot,
in a village near Toledo.
How long did it take you to prepare the shot in the village near Toledo?
Five months.
When the kite stands out, when they will feel true ...
what you say, when ...
when they will be sure they can get information ...
with the left hand pull the thread
and stop the kite.
Take time.
Do you wear boxers, Colonel?
I always thought that the military liked wide underpants.
- Am I wrong? - Wide underpants!
Can anyone tell me why this woman is in these conditions?
Excuse us.
I'm happy to see you again, Miss Tokio.
This time we will be practical, I ask and she answers.
Who is the Professor?
- Ready? - Hello! I have to talk...
with Inspector Raquel Murillo, please, it's urgent.
Who wants it?
It's a personal matter.
Inspector Murillo, urgent call.
Answer as well.
I do not move from here.
It is a personal matter.
- Who's talking? - Raquel, thank goodness! I'm...
I'm saving, I call you from the police station, they arrested me.
They accuse me of attacking ...
a public official. Your husband, to be precise.
Don't ask why!
I'm handcuffed and talk about ...
four years imprisonment or worse.
In which police station are you?
- In that of Canillas. - Do not worry.
- I'll be here as soon as possible.  - Thanks.
Let's continue.
I was about to talk about the Professor.
Her short hair, inspector, would be much better.
So he looks a little too maternal.
I'm really keen to tell you everything.
excellent
Perfect, because I'm here with open arms waiting for him to do it.
Look at the bright side...
now you will not have to escape anymore.
Now it's time to start from scratch.
Do you want to know how everything started?
The professor picked me up.
With a red Seat Ibiza.
While the police were ambushing me.
No
No, no, it started all before.
A child.
His name was Miguel.
He pulled my underwear down in front of the whole class.
Do you think I was expelled instead of that six-year-old little shit?
From that moment, everything went to hell.
Is it true what they said before?
Did you tie a policeman?
You must say that there was a fight.
If you hit it only you ...
you're in the shit.
I see you all too well, to be honest.
Excuse me, can I go to the bathroom?
Keep an eye on it.
I did not come here to be a nurse.
Neither to hear speeches nor to do shit therapies.
First I had to shut up so as not to make the situation in the group worse.
It is a good thing...
that you worry about your companions.
Do you know what really worries me?
The Professor, Berlin ...
there is not!
There is only you.
And he is the brain.
Just because it's the brain organized ...
a perfect plan that we will follow ...
step by step, without doing anything that he did not foresee.
You've already done something unexpected,
you sent Tokyo.
Tokyo will have its part, if it behaves well ...
and he says nothing.
Bullshits! His part would have obtained it in case of capture ...
not in case you throw it down the stairs straight up straight to the lions.
With the shitty character he has, do you know what he's done? He will have told everything.
And the GEO will be in the hangar ...
to dig the tunnel on the other side to break in.
You can put your complaints in the suggestion box,
but unfortunately, as you could see with Rio,
it will not do any good, because this is a patriarchy.
- And what would you like to say? - It means that I command here!
And if you do not want to do the same thing ...
of Rio and Tokyo, I suggest you to have a camomile.
What the fuck is he taking you, Nairobi?
Did you synchronize the cycle with Tokyo?
We are similar.
I do not think my life is as exciting as yours.
No, I do not believe it either.
But it should not be easy to wear the skirt in the police body.
And it's not even in a gang of robbers.
We are few.
For this reason, we have to pull the balls out continuously.
Is it true?
Does not it seem exhausting?
Silene ...
I think you're wasting my time.
And you're playing any penalty reduction.
Every minute that passes ...
It's a year more.
Listen ...
you're young now.
He is hot. You do not miss anything.
In twelve years you will still be in shape.
Maybe with some wrinkles, even interesting.
But if you will be released in 24 years ...
you will have entered menopause.
And that ...
that's a different matter, is not it, Prieto?
I know because of his mother.
And I do not mean the hot flashes,
but to the feeling ...
to have lost something important.
Something intrinsically yours ...
that will have vanished forever.
Your Life.
Inspector.
Does he really see me in a park as a family mother?
To change diapers?
But please.
Listen
I give you the last chance before calling the investigating judge.
If you do not speak, many greetings.
Finish immediately for precautionary custody.
And you will not have discounts for collaboration, repentance ...
and mitigating factors.
And it would be 10-12 years of life.
So think carefully before throwing everything in the wind.
Do you want a tip?
Sure.
Think of a nice place.
At a moment in life where you were really happy.
And breathe deeply.
Reflect.
Tokyo!
I can't take it anymore.
You can not do it.
They drugged you like a horse.
A hypnotic sedative.
Get relaxed.
And enjoy it.
Water 100
Please.
Go back to sleep.
How the fuck do I sleep?
If I do not stop dreaming Tokyo.
Tokyo is a daughter of a bitch.
Don't ask why!
Do you know what your girlfriend did with the only hope of my life?
When did he last see you? He was three years old, was not he?
He put it in his mouth, he chewed it and spit it in my face.
- He does not remember a shit about you. - Close that fucking mouth!
- You do not remember, it will not recognize you. - Shut up.
But do you know what's the worst?
It is that he is right.
He is right.
I would have kidnapped a child ...
who has no idea who I am.
And now I have no idea what to do with all that money.
Listen.
Maybe not now ...
but in a few years you can look for it and ...
and you can explain everything to him.
You say to him: "Listen, fuck ...
I'm your mother. "
"I am richly broken and I live in Jamaica."
"If you want to know the full story, I'll buy you an airplane and come to meet me."
And then, you're young.
You have two ovaries, right?
You can do another one.
Already.
Five minutes, no more.
Easy, no?
Listen.
Would you give me a child? Would you give it to me?
Sure.
How do you want it, blond or dark?
No kidding.
If I go out of here, I need to have a reason ...
to live.
Listen ...
What can I tell you, Nairobi?
Make a child to have a reason to live ...
It does not seem like a good plan.
No
- And then, I'm with Tokyo, not ... - I'm not asking you to marry me.
I'm just asking you a little ...
of sperm.
Two spintarelle and it's done, impregnated.
Because you are so attractive and intelligent ...
and with that beautiful smile you have ...
it would be so easy.
Stop! It's so easy!
If you lose a child, do another, do not you?
Because in the end it only matters to have ...
- a reason to live. - Fuck!
Damn bitch, you say Tokio is crazy, but you're worse!
- Where are you going? - To that country.
No, no, stop.
No
We have to rub Berlin without having to deliver.
Save
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
I messed up everything, I'm very sorry.
- What did that animal do to you? - No, no, no.
It was not just his fault, I ...
I talked about what he did to you, about the mistreatment of your sister.
- Fuck. - I like it a lot. Really.
I'm not so usually, I do not know what got me, but ...
the blood boiled.
I'm not a violent, I've never beaten anyone.
Never, I am one who solves things by speaking calmly.
Did you defend yourself?
Well, I'm not Mohamed Ali, but ...
but I have my pride and ...
I gave them to him. I played them ...
for good.
But now I feel like a punching bag.
- I think he won. - Let me see.
Wait!
Fuck.
I immediately call a doctor to let you visit, quiet.
- I'll handle that. - Thank you.
I tell you that I'm attending one and two seconds time are you fighting?
He hit me, I did not even touch him.
- I want you to withdraw the complaint immediately. - Self?
Collect that against me.
This story will help you a lot in the cause we have ...
beating my partner, I mean.
That chuck of Chuck Norris wearing glasses made me lose consciousness.
You can tell bullshit your lawyer.
It will not help you with custody.
Raquel.
I did not do anything, I did not touch it.
No? Come with me.
I'm Inspector Raquel Murillo, from the plant.
I want to know who drafted the report against this man.
And because he did not visit a doctor since he was beaten by this agent.
Save
open your shirt.
This man would like to complain about abuse of power ...
and you need to prepare a medical report.
You will all be witnesses in the report.
Raquel, I do not know how fucking she's done, but I swear I did not touch her.
The victim has bruises on the chest, ribs and abdomen.
He was clearly beaten up.
Someone is writing the report, yes or no?
Raquel.
Agree.
Leave it.
Withdraw the complaint.
very good
Then he will withdraw his.
Remove the cuffs.
Where are your personal effects?
Raquel, I would not look like a paranoid conspiracy theorist, but there are ...
my prints and my data around, do not ...
Right.
Where's the record of his arrest?
Let's go, save.
I had never felt so lost.
I had nothing left.
I just had to decide whether to betray my companions ...
hoping for the clemency of the judge as a collaborator.
Do you want to say something?
Someone could fry an egg, please?
Fuck.
I've been eating craps for four days.
Tokyo, I will not abandon you, I have thought of everything.
And then, I'm a lucky man.
You must never forget it.
Tokyo, I will not abandon you.
I can not handle it anymore.
It is the thirtieth chest like this.
He does not care if he has a gunshot wound.
I do not even want to think about the repercussions we will have, especially psychological ones.
Having to come and work here every day.
Having to relive it continuously.
Well, it will be difficult for everyone.
And it is possible that some of us will suffer from post-traumatic stress.
Well, I have all the right credentials.
I do not know what is more traumatic than losing everything.
I lost everything ...
and these do not compensate.
Quite the contrary.
About one million euros ...
it makes me laugh.
You trust all of those who keep us locked up ...
- as if we were beasts. - Do you finish it?
- Sorry? - Close that fucking mouth.
Please, Alison.
I'm sick of listening to this here that complains.
If you do not like it, do something, do not you?
Even I was complaining about everything.
Of my parents...
of the school where I was bulled.
I swallowed one toad after another.
- Enough!
Honey, it's normal to see everything black right now.
8 - Unlike many smartphones
It will have ruined your life ...
but he opened my eyes.
I realized that we are what we eat.
And I do not know about you, but I've had enough of eating shit.
So I'm leaving.
Alison, do not talk nonsense.
I am your guardian and responsible for your safety, so as long as you are ...
She is here for the money.
Your bribe may be good for you ...
and being accomplices of these carrions. But not me.
And then it's not so difficult to get out of here.
Get out of here?
How?
I just need to hurt myself.
They will take me to another place ...
and from there I can escape.
No, no and no. Do not even think about doing such stupid things.
Mercedes, Mercedes ...
let the girl explain herself.
I've seen it more than ten times since we've been here.
Press the button and the door only takes four seconds to open.
Four seconds and run out ...
you do not need anything else.
Four seconds are enough and they move forward to shoot you.
We'll see.
How are you, hostages?
The million euro makes you sleep peacefully?
So keep on dreaming ...
because no one will give it to you.
It's a lie...
as well as that your companions have been freed ...
those who chose to leave instead of a million, no.
Two floors are underneath you.
- What a fool. - Chained to the pipes.
It was a strategy ...
to make you stay calm like sheep while you work for us.
But with a smile on your lips ...
because here we must always be smiling!
True or not, Mr. Andrés de Fonollosa ...
that we do not want long faces?
Are you done?
We will not get out of the hole you are digging, no ...
we will go out of one who comes directly into the safe.
You are guilty of high treason, Rio.
It is unforgivable.
- Here we go. - Come on, let's go.
Are there any news?
No, he did not say anything.
Apparently, Miss Tokio does not intend to cooperate.
Colonel ...
a question.
The deputy inspector Rubio told her something about a teaspoon?
A teaspoon?
No because?
Ángel had it analyzed before having the accident ...
the fingerprints coincide with those of the subject ...
that forced the steering wheel to threaten the Russian.
It is the same person who helps them from the outside.
- And who the hell is he? - I do not know.
I will be the same person who tampered with Ángel's car and caused the accident.
But only Ángel knows this.
And she.
Tell me something.
Stay silent for everyone ...
or just for Aníbal Cortés?
You see that you are in love, in this picture.
How about if I offer you two for one?
Is there a happy hour?
I offer him the same agreement that I offer to you.
Mitigation, repentance and collaboration.
Provided that the information you give us will serve to put an end word ...
to this nightmare.
We are talking about a third of the sentence.
It's impossible...
we have so many crimes that we can spend more lives in prison ...
no judge can promise us so much.
Even less her.
Look, I do not know what they told you but if you regret ...
collaborate and help save the lives of fifty victims ...
I assure you that any judge will be kind.
Aníbal Cortés is not guilty of personal injury.
- In five years it would be out. - At 24,
as if he had just graduated.
I think it's a better plan than doing the end ...
about your last boyfriend ...
do not you think?
It was a very bad idea to talk to the hostages, Rio.
You can even throw me out like Tokyo.
Tied up for good.
- Because I'm not going to shut up. - I trust in Tokyo ...
but you are a brat.
What a pity. He thinks that paradox, Helsinki.
Tokyo ...
he'll shut up to protect him.
And yet, you will disappear without her knowing it.
What will you do to me?
What you begged me to do.
Execute you.
In fact, you've lost your mind.
I can not allow you to leave ...
but neither do you remain
What you said to the hostages was your sentence and I will not shake my hand.
Well, actually it trembles a little.
That's right.
It is important to face death with spirit.
Who, like me, acts in an inconsiderate way ...
it's not that he cares about the consequences ...
No
he cares like anyone else.
It's just that we only get aware of it when it's too late.
We only become aware of it when we face it.
Do you want to say your last words?
You can still learn from your mistakes and stop being an asshole.
Mamma mia, Helsinki!
This boy just became a man.
If you had not died so early, you could have been a new Paulo Coelho.
What a pity...
- the world will have to do without it. - Berlin!
What the fuck are you doing?
Lower the gun.
Discussion time is over.
Unfortunately, democracy only gave us problems and I just issued the sentence.
Enough bullshit, we have all the nerves on edge.
Berlin, we do not make things worse.
Berlin...
we can not make war between us.
Turn it down.
Berlin.
See to lower that gun or you'll see the green mice in pain ...
I found your painkillers.
What are you going to do...
Nairobi? Break the vials one by one like Tokyo did?
Well, you know what it is, I have the cycle.
But how we are gossip, we women, is not it?
And how we get angry if one passes where we have washed.
Son of a bitch!
Berlin, you have a lost call, honey.
Come on, stop.
That's enough.
very good
you chose.
Bad, but you chose.
Take it away.
And at that moment I saw myself clearly ...
in court...
in jail.
And I understood that the inspector was right ...
that it was not worth sacrificing for a failed plan ...
for the Professor's plan.
Especially because I thought he had deceived me.
Sergio!
His name is Sergio.
One moment.
Let her talk.
The Professor is called Sergio Marquina.
And the shot is an idea of ​​his father.
And the person who helps you from the outside, who is he?
Inspector ...
they are calling from the tick.
How are you, how was your day?
Well, I would say well.
To tell the truth, I was a little worried about her.
I thought we would not talk ...
that something irreparable had happened to her.
Sergio.
It's kind of worrying, inspector, but ...
I am a lucky man, he must never forget it.
I simply called her to say hello ...
I leave her to question Tokio, she has many things to tell her.
And as soon as it's finished ...
call me.
That from here I do not move.
What do you have to tell me?
They kicked me to give you a message in person.
Inside, we have a hydrogen bomb of seventeen megatons.
We'll blow it out tomorrow at twelve.
I'd like to talk to a priest.
I must confess.
excellent
we will propose detention in isolation, without bail
Gómez ...
draft the report and underline the lack of collaboration and repentance.
Have it lead to the nearest prison.
Lobo, take it away.
- Control call. - Here, everything is as smooth as oil.
Like oil?
Like oil, do you mean Tokyo interrogated by the police?
Like oil, do you mean that Rio did not do justice to you?
Berlin, what are you doing?
Professor, I'm Nairobi.
Berlin is not doing very well ...
so, starting now, I'm in charge.
The matriarchy begins.
In the next episode ...
We have to do something, steal a weapon from him.
- Where do we find a gun? - Replacing it with a false one.
Your accomplice Silene Oliveira from tonight will be in custody without bail.
- Nairobi is now in charge. - You decide, you're with me ...
or against me?
I will release eleven hostages ...
I want a journalist and a cameraman to cover the news from inside.
Let's leave.
I close the cider in a couple of days ...
and we leave together in a Caribbean country.
I try to take the gun ...
give me good luck.
Let's move on to the Cameroon floor.
Deputy Inspector Rubio, will leave the coma.
Go make sure it's not a trap. If it was not ...
you will have to delete it.
We organize the operation ...
but on the spot we will be there to take it with our hands in the bag.
Let's go, fast.
The hostages, fuck!
Do not open the door!