Translated by the community of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Inspector, we found the property.
You have to scour every single corner of this house.
All the plan, fuck.
Hours, photos, programs.
It makes no sense. Call Alberto ...
Is not it the best of the scientific? So, come on.
All they wanted to eliminate seriously ...
they will have burned him in here.
I take this to the central of Canillas.
I really had to go to Madrid, I would have taken the bus.
I was thinking back to what you said before ...
to the fact that you wish the best of Raquel.
If so, you do not ...
he discovered his sister.
- Piece of shit. - Get out of the car.
Son of a bitch.
You are under arrest for assault on a public official.
Give me the revolver.
Tell us about the Chernobil plan.
I'm the only one in here who knows the plan.
You will not have the slightest idea how to get out of this fucking trap.
Listen to me, it could not be the beginning ...
of a wonderful friendship?
Take off your boots and tracksuit, fast!
Do not shoot.
Tokyo.
- Fuck. - Rio ...
- you must calm down. - No, you sent Tokyo to jail.
She's my girlfriend and you ruined her life.
Perhaps you do not realize why you are here against your will, Mónica ...
but you have a syndrome.
- What syndrome? - Of Stockholm.
Speech closed. You continue on your way ...
I for mine, without looking back.
The Professor, Berlin, is not there!
There is only you. And he is the brain.
This is a patriarchy.
- And what would you like to say? - It means that I command here.
I can go to the bathroom?
I call you from the police station, they arrested me.
I tell you that I'm attending one and two seconds time are you fighting?
- I have not done anything. - No?
Come with me.
I do not know how the fuck is done but I swear I did not touch it.
Remove the cuffs.
I'm happy to see you again, Miss Tokio.
I ask and she answers.
Who is the Professor?
Very good, you have chosen.
Bad, but you have chosen.
Take it away.
Sergio!
The Professor is called Sergio Marquina.
And the blow is an idea of ​​his father.
And the person who helps you from the outside, who is he?
Inspector, I just called to say hello ...
let me interrogate Tokio.
That from here I do not move.
- What is it you have to tell me? - Inside, we have a hydrogen bomb ...
of seventeen megatons.
We will propose detention in isolation.
Lobo, take it away.
It was a very bad idea to talk to the hostages, Rio.
You can even throw me out like Tokyo.
You are guilty of high treason, Rio.
- What will you do to me? - Execute yourself.
Lower the gun.
Control call.
Here, everything is as smooth as oil.
Like oil?
Like oil, do you mean Tokyo interrogated by the police?
Like oil, you mean that for a while ...
did not you do Rio?
Berlin, what are you doing?
Professor, I'm Nairobi.
Berlin is not doing very well ...
so, starting now, I'm in charge.
The matriarchy begins.
If we took a picture now ...
it could be my last memory of the State Mint.
In there I left a series of errors ...
a band in pieces ...
and only one kidnapper with balls to load everything on his shoulder ...
Nairobi.
What I mean, Professor, and that's a mess here.
The measure has been lost inside.
Tokio played Russian roulette with Berlin tied to a chair.
And Berlin handed it to the police.
So Rio defected,
and Berlin almost did not shoot her in Vietnam style, fuck.
And then Helsinki suffocated Oslo.
Did he kill him?
It was a vegetable, now ...
according to Helsinki, that's what he wanted.
As you can see, Professor, everything went to hell here.
So
I have to take the reins in my hands until the waters have calmed down.
Ask him what the fuck was he doing with the police?
I was in the house of Toledo because it was part of the plan.
Professor ...
here we need to know what situation we are in.
MONDAY 9:00 PM
There are some problems, I'll be honest.
83 HOURS FROM THE BEGINNING OF THE RAPINA
I would call it the biggest "problemino" in history.
Deputy Inspector Ángel had discovered the identity of the Professor.
He had isolated his fingerprints.
At the moment he was in a coma, but he would have told it as soon as he was awake.
The Professor had the days counted.
And with him, also all the others.
And the situation there is not better, from what you tell me.
Listen ...
do what you owe out there,   in the meantime I'll fix things in here.
And now I'll give you the call that is definitely the inspector.
Inspector.
Before returning to us, I would like to take a doubt ...
from now on as you want me to call you ...
Professor ...
Sergio, or ...
Mr. Marquina?
For her I will always be the Professor.
That's how we met, right?
I will always remember her as Inspector Murillo.
Even if one day he became my executioner.
Remember the first time he made love?
Of course, that never forgets, no?
Well, this is my first time ...
in the world of crime.
And in any way it will go, it will be forever ...
a nice memory.
You are passionate ...
and this world needs people like her.
I hope when he gets out of prison fully rehabilitated ...
is dedicated to waking up this country because the truth is that ...
Where was it?
Don't ask why!
His first time.
In a field tent.
How nice.
That's a nice place for a first time.
The murmur of the countryside, the light ...
Yes, that yes ...
while the rest, let's say ...
he was improvised ...
E 01.01.2016
no frills.
Well, Professor ...
I called her to inform her that her accomplice, Silene Oliveira,
from tonight ...
will be under precautionary custody without the possibility of bail, from tonight.
What did he say to make her angry so much that he did not take advantage of the 72 hours of detention?
He did a little too gorgeous.
But one thing I do not understand ...
why get out ...
a robber rather than a hostage?
Let's say that misunderstandings have arisen in the group, nothing more.
We put you on the ropes, Professor.
-  And you know it.  - It's true, it's the advantage, inspector ...
but this is just a battle ...
something insignificant if you compare it to war.
Keep teasing her despite the mutiny.
Is good.
Save ...
how are you?
Are your bruises still bad?
Well!
I never imagined that lacing my shoes could do so badly.
It is clear that those bruises need treatment ...
of a nurse.
It's
very tempting proposal.
I'd really like to take care of you, but ...
we should meet with me, because I want to see my daughter, and ...
I know it's not the most romantic plan in the world.
I could not imagine a better plan for tonight.
okay.
When you spend years thinking obsessively about something ...
that something becomes your world.
A perfect world.
But now the plan was no longer just the Professor ...
it was everyone's.
And we were sending him all a bit to hell.
The Professor felt unarmed, for once ...
and burrowing himself in Raquel's arms seemed to him the best refuge ...
the only possible.
Now you're a hostage too.
What happened to you?
They tried to kill me ...
they almost shot me.
Why did they want to kill you?
They gave Tokyo to the police ...
and I wanted to deliver myself too.
- Alison. - Leave it, let it.
- Let her. - That girl has lost her mind ...
- if Tokio arrived, who knows what he would do to her. - You will not come, you heard, they kicked her out.
What Alison is doing can make us comfortable.
- Make us comfortable for what? - To get out of here, fuck ...
once and for all.
Fucking, is it so hard to understand?
They locked up our comrades ...
when they had promised him freedom.
Some of us have been deeply humiliated.
They ruined my relationship ...
and my future fatherhood.
And as for the money that they promised us to stay in this hell ...
It's all a lie.
A fucking farce.
He confirmed it.
Until when do we want to stay with our hands in our hands?
The robbers are now in trouble ...
it is indisputable ...
and do not take advantage of this opportunity right away ...
means to let them escape.
We must give him the coup de grace.
Recover your dignity, fuck, courage,
this wild beast that we keep hidden and ...
Yes, we have to do something ...
□ I don't know
steal a weapon from him.
As? What do you say, Arturo?
Where do we find a gun?
Replacing it with a fake.
If you can get one of the fake guns ...
you can exchange it.
So one of them will be disarmed ...
and one of you, armed.
The house de papel - 1x12 Cuestión de eficacia
Hey, hi, honey.
- Mom, what are you doing here so late? - Mom.
Honey, come here.
It's fine
But then, you ...
- What are you doing here so late? - I did not want to go to bed without saying goodbye.
Neither me, my life.
Bye.
But why did not you warn? I would have prepared dinner for you.
You came to have dinner, right?
Yes, well, to have dinner and even to sleep ...
don't you?
Are you coming out together?
Well!
Yes No?
More or less.
But did you ask her?
Well, no, actually not, but ...
but we kissed, that's ...
almost the same thing.
- All right. - Come on, Paulita, honey, let's go ...
Let's go, you'll have school tomorrow.
Let's go to bed. No, stay there ...
I put her in bed.
Thank you.
Is it true that you beat him?
Well!
Well ... yes.
It is that blood boiled at the thought that he had put his hands on you.
I do not like violence, I do not ...
never liked it. I know you should not use it and that you know how to defend yourself very well from you ...
- and I do not have the right to put myself ... - Save.
I'm glad you gave slaps to that wretch of my ex ...
I should have done it.
Although it is politically incorrect to say so.
Well!
sometimes the politically incorrect is ...
the only option.
I tell you from experience.
I'm glad you're here.
Well, from now on you have to take care of closing the bags ...
- tirelessly. - Lies says nothing.
Arturito is not the time to make Gandhi, because you would receive punches for breakfast,
lunch and dinner.
Plus I can assure you ...
that I have not lied to anyone.
In command now there is Nairobi ...
so get everyone to close the bags.
Nairobi has a wrist to be a woman.
Berlin...
we are going to peak.
So I think the most important thing now ...
both come out alive from here ...
without making other mistakes.
You decide...
you are with me...
or against me?
A bi bo ...
who's underneath I do not know ...
- but I will soon know it. - but I will soon know it.
All right, Nairobi, I'll follow you ...
till death.
I will respect your coup ...
and I must confess that I even feel excited ...
the idea of ​​serving a woman who seems so divine.
Well, you'd better venerate this goddess ...
because he has your morphine, do not forget it.
That's the office where fake guns hide.
- IS? - One of us must go there ...
and take up arms.
And which robber do you think you care about the real one?
In Denver.
It is the most stupid.
- And who will take the gun? - Mónica will have to do it,
- taking advantage of when the gauze changes. - And why should he do something like that?
It's suicide.
Because that bullet shot her ...
he locked her in a hole and took advantage of her fear and despair ...
to get fucked.
And it seems that now he left her, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
But it went like this.
Sometimes we would like to change life ...
we make illusions ...
but no robber will ever take you away with him.
Alright then.
I'll take care of the gun.
Do you have copies of the office keys?
What is the Chernobil plan?
The Chernobil plan is a plan ...
desperate, but very cute ...
it consisted of throwing the banknotes from the roof with balloons ...
and blow up the balloons with the guns causing a wonderful rain,
- then call media, radio, television ... - It would be like the parade of the Magi Kings ...
but with 50-dollar bills.
Is this the Chernobil plan?
Thousands of people gathering the grain, the most total chaos in the police, imagine ...
- 1000 million euros falling from the sky. - Yeah ...
while we run away in the hubbub.
Very nice.
You know that the Professor is an idealist ...
the message matters more than money.
And I have not told you anything because you have to respect the times.
Give me good luck.
Mr. Torres ...
At my office.
Come on, Mr. Torres.
So,
could we increase the printing rhythm?
for power, we could ...
but we would take a big risk ...
if it gets jammed ...
it would take three or four hours to fix the car.
Calculations of how much we would increase production.
All right, Miss Nairobi.
Don Arturo?
Get up.
Get up, Torres, fuck, get up.
- What are you doing there? - It's not your business.
Listen to me, pretend nothing ...
go straight to the door and do not close it from outside.
I'm sorry, but I'll have to say about her.
If they find out I've seen it, it will be trouble for me too.
Listen
puppet subspecies ...
I have a gun.
If you dare to do the spy ...
the first bullet is all yours, understand?
Excuse me, Don Arturo, but that gun is fake ...
he also left the bag open.
Listen to me...
listen to me well because I will not say it twice.
When it's all over ...
and I assure you that, at most, they remain just two hours ...
you will come back here ...
at your shit job.
And the next day you will find me waiting for you ...
with a letter of dismissal ...
and a disciplinary procedure that you do not even imagine.
You will see the green mice up to retirement ...
Do you understand? ...
If I'm not mistaken you have three daughters, right?
And two of them are unemployed from around ...
seven years? If memory does not deceive me.
So you decide ...
Torres.
- Miss Nairobi. - Tell me.
Productivity would increase by two million per hour.
Just do it.
And what's more ...
we will do the technical stops every six hours ...
- so will be another two million more. - Agree.
Of this I am sure, as it is true that my name is Nairobi.
Is there something that worries you?
No
No, it worries me that it was the best night of my life.
Save
you already have me in hand, you do not need to exaggerate.
It's true.
The fact is that I had not foreseen it, I had not calculated it.
You did not calculate it.
And what does it mean, what do you calculate everything?
Well, let's say ...
that I am a man who ...
choose the clothes to wear the day before.
A man who has fixed himself ...
with the idea ...
to make the best cider in the world.
and right now... you are?
and I studied everything, I studied ...
acidity, fermentation ...
every possible answer of each ingredient.
Year...
after year, after year.
And just that an apple is not good ...
to ruin the whole barrel.
Save, maybe you've exaggerated with cider, do not you think?
It was a dream that my father had.
But...
he died before he realized it.
carefully.
he wanted to do ...
2,400 barrels.
I understand the tribute to the memory, but ...
I do not know, why do not you make half of it?
Or half of the half, and ...
And than...
you dedicate yourself to your dreams.
Let's leave.
I solve this cider thing in a few days and ...
and you and I leave you in a Caribbean country.
Well!
IO-01
I do not have cider to do, but ...
but I have a mother and a daughter and ...
- and a robbery to end. - So let's take your mother ...
and your daughter and we bring them with us.
You can not see your daughter ...
to grow on a beach under the sun?
Raquel.
Raquel, I do not want it to end.
I do not want to ignore this ...
this desire that I feel alive, because I've never had so much.
You would cross the ocean with ...
with a mother ...
a daughter and ...
a grandmother?
Right now, yes.
It's a plan B.
It is that it is ...
so crazy that ...
that
that I do not see myself doing anything else.
Close the robbery speech, do what you have to do.
And then we leave.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Listen to me all ...
we will end this robbery in 24 hours ...
and we will return to our lives, which we have already neglected enough.
Suárez ...
he calls Commissioner Sánchez.
I will not let anyone else die ...
neither that you destroy from within nor that you capture. So, Nairobi ...
listen to me, the fact that you have arrived here is already something epic ...
so I'll give you my most sincere congratulations.
Listen to me well ...
I will get you out of there ...
before they get you out.
Also bring Lobo and others from the Central Operations Service.
- What are you thinking, inspector? - I start thinking ...
that the man who is outside is the real brain of the operation.
It is he who has filled the way with clues to take us to the estate of Toledo ...
but I think I know how to take it.
The first thing we will do is get the hostages out of the basement.
Well, thank you, because we do not have so many people to control the hostages.
And then we promised him freedom, right?
That they have freedom, then.
We will free those hostages, but give me an hour.
It's too big a show for such a small audience.
- Hello?
I will free 11 hostages.
But on one condition ...
I want a journalist and a cameraman to come in ...
to cover the news from the inside, a direct link.
Look ...
I'd like to help her with her propaganda, but ...
I can not force any civilian to go in there ...
-  he knows this well.  - It's true.
He is completely right, inspector.
But she does not have to force anyone, she just has to propose it.
I'm sure there will be many journalists ...
volunteers for an interview like this.
- I have to think about it. - Of course, think about it.
But remember that I record these conversations and the last time ...
who refused to free the hostages ...
let's say he did not make a big impression with public opinion.
Anyway, of course, take your time.
What a son of a bitch.
God.
Well, let's talk about something else. As I can explain it, let's see ...
Do you like football?
Football, Professor. In what world do you think ...
Well, then imagine ...
- a soccer match. - Still with football?
No, no, Nairobi, listen. A World Cup football match ...
and they are playing Brazil and Cameroon.
- Who win? - Well ...
Sorry, I express myself better ...
who do you want to win?
To win, Brazil wins.
But I would support for Cameroon, for sure.
- Cameroon. - Yup.
- Cameroon, Cameroon. - Cameroon or death.
If you notice ...
instinctively human being ...
always puts on the side ...
of the weakest ...
of losers.
So if we show the world our weaknesses, our ...
wounds ...
that we are on the point ...
to surrender ...
we will produce a ...
emotion.
Apart from the Brazilians, I think anyone would cheer Cameroon.
Even some Brazilian.
- Or Brazilian. - Or Brazilian.
Gentlemen, strength, force Cameroon then, no?
How's that song you sing at games?
Cameroon, Cameroon, Cameroon.
Cameroon ...
Cameroon!
Let's move on to the Cameroon floor.
We will free the hostages who are in the basement ...
and a journalist and a cameraman will come back to the scene.
We will need someone to do the interview.
And my choice ...
it's you, Rio.
I understand you're pissed off, but we need you.
You can do it without a mask ...
You're nice...
Do you really think I want to end up on TV?
So does Tokio see me from prison?
With a toothy smile ...
while they interview me as if a fuck did not happen here?
I'm a hostage now, right?
Do not count on me.
Fuck it, I'll do it.
I have a poor loser's face, I've always had it.
You do not have a loser face ...
you have the face to wear.
I'll do it.
If you do not have to talk a lot.
It's an idea. It's an idea.
But no, no.
I'll do it, with the mask.
With the mask.
A live interview?
What we are?
ETA?
Jihadists?
No, no, no.
This interview must be done ...
with the face uncovered.
So that all of Spain ...
can perceive our looks ...
our breath ...
that can perceive pain.
And even a little 'suffering.
Yeah
In short, do you want to do it?
Is that...
You know what?
If there is a person I have never seen, try neither suffering nor pain ...
that one is you.
Berlin.
Tokyo is not there.
And Rio does not want to do it.
Do not despise those who can do their job well, Nairobi.
I can be a perfect master of ceremonies.
He is right.
He knows how to act very well.
very good
You will do it.
A live interview in exchange for the release of eleven hostages.
It's more...
justifiable, no?
They will cut us apart.
But we can only accept.
We try to turn the thing to our advantage ...
presenting it as a transparency operation.
You can sell it as you wish, Prieto.
But the other thing?
The operation you want to organize at the hospital?
In exchange for what, based on what, Raquel?
Of a plate of anchovies?
Based on the fact that the robbers have an external aide ...
that puts us the sticks in the wheels.
Ángel knows who he is ...
- and they almost killed him, other than an accident. - Provincial.
Here we have read the scientific report on the Ángel incident ...
and there is no evidence that it was attempted murder.
Let's not forget that he drove in a state of intoxication.
Alright...
Do you want some tests?
We organize the operation.
Let me leap to the press that Ángel ...
the only person who knows who he is ...
he will wake up from the coma.
And I assure you that by five in the afternoon ...
that man will be in the hospital to kill him.
But we will be there too, to capture him like a cat and a mouse.
You're asking me to fill a hospital ...
of undercover agents, in style ...
Mortadello and Polpetta.
We should concentrate our resources here on the mint.
Have you thought about the journalists we'll let in?
And if they took them hostage?
The interview is just a smoke screen.
Another trick to make us waste time.
- Inspector.
let me for once ...
we are trying to set a trap.
Are ten men enough?
Twenty.
Monica Gaztambide, it's time for treatment.
Come on.
If you take off your suit, I can cure you.
Can you turn around?
We're not together anymore, are we?
No problem.
May I?
Wait!
1 hour
How's the wound?
It hurts me very much.
And it burns me.
We will only have one chance.
I want it alive.
Nobody pulls the trigger, except in extreme cases.
The first thing we will do ...
it will take Ángel away and put it in a safe place.
For this reason
we will have to prepare another room on another floor.
Once it is safe, we will leak the news of his recovery.
And the goal will not be slow to get going.
By then, it is essential that everyone is in place.
I want everyone to fall in the part to the core ...
It is a very complex operation.
And we will need extreme concentration.
We will have access to the video surveillance system.
None of the security in the whole area. Not even the security of the hospital.
Nor flying in the immediate vicinity.
We'll spread a nice red carpet to that fucker up to Angel's bed.
Where will you find Lobo.
And Agent Valmaseda will take over from María Carmen.
They will be there waiting for him to welcome him.
Remember that we are looking for a middle-aged man.
There will be twenty agents and he will be alone.
It is difficult to escape.
You did?
Give me, fast.
It is charged.
Just pack up banknotes ...
and put away those you can.
We're leaving.
Here. Put them away.
Here.
Fast!
We're leaving.
It also lasted too much.
Fuck.
Come on.
Fifth day of seizure.
A hostage and two wounded policemen.
An explosion.
An escapade of hostages.
And now the cameras of the Sexta ...
will enter the place ...
that the whole world is observing.
Journalists are near the entrance.
Cristina, we must remember the historical importance of what we are experiencing.
Hundreds of channels in the whole world transmit our live ...
Cover them until they are entered.
It's the first time that a television crew enters the scenario ...
They open the doors. Spare men, watch out.
Stop by the foot of the stairs as they requested.
Special Mint of the State.
Crucial moment.
In less than a minute ...
JOURNEY TO THE CENTER OF THE SEQUESTRO
we will live something historical.
A journalist and a cameraman of the Sixth ...
will enter the place of the seizure.
The police arrive up there.
It's the deal, from then on ...
the journalist and the cameraman continue alone ...
without protection.
He had never seen something like this.
The streets of the whole country are empty.
Return to position.
- Hello, good morning. - Good morning.
I am Andrés de Fonollosa.
Thank you both for coming.
Can you put this, please?
Yes.
We already receive the signal ...
let's move on to live ...
from inside the Mint.
Mr. Fonollosa, I have to ask you why he allowed a news crew ...
broadcast live from here.
This is ...
a decisive moment for all those in here and ...
your presence was necessary to resume it and make it public.
Please come with me. Come on.
That is Andrés de Fonollosa,
one of the faces known to the police.
Robber, informant and convicted of trafficking in human beings.
These are the eleven hostages ...
that will finally be released.
Here they are.
I acknowledge...
Manuel Garcia.
Alfonso Martínez.
And María Cornejo.
It really seems to release them.
We're all nervous.
Prepare medical assistance.
Almost like children about to go out during recreation.
I want to thank everyone.
For the audacity and courage ...
that you have demonstrated.
and right now... you are?
to you in particular ...
to you and your creature.
You have proven to be a strong woman.
Because you decided right now,
after five days of captivity ...
to free the hostages?
Five days.
It seems impossible to believe that only a few days have passed, is not it?
You see ...
we must confess that it is a difficult time for us ...
the situation is critical.
We just have to give up.
And that's why you're here.
This gesture is the beginning of the end for everyone.
Helsinki.
The moment has come.
They can go.
Thank you.
Snipers ready.
Squad one assault, keep your distance.
Got it.
We will begin to free the hostages and try to negotiate a surrender ...
that meets our interests.
Have you decided to give yourself to the police?
We realized we had lost.
Open the doors!
- Eleven released, we see them. Finally ...  - They are coming out.
good news from the State Mint.
Here they are, a very emotional moment.
It seems the band starts to give in.
But there's more news, great news.
Fonollosa recognizes that the situation is critical,
who are forced to surrender.
The exact words were: "This is the beginning of the end."
and right now... you are?
"We realized we had lost".
I do not know if you've ever seen a body before.
Even for some of us it is the first time.
She came here to tell the truth.
Here, this is the truth.
We've been beaten,
we have been defeated.
It is important to confirm this ...
please.
Yes.
There is no beat, he is dead.
The hostages who escaped hit him in the head.
He died after a couple of hours.
It's possible for people out there,
this man is nothing but a thief.
But for us it was a companion and a friend.
Nobody prepares you for such a thing.
Nobody. It is one of the reasons that led us to free the hostages.
Some of us have always thought that they would not come out alive here, but ...
I never thought it would be him.
What does it mean?
There were people in the group ...
ready to sacrifice?
No, no.
No
I did not mean that. We are simple people.
People who lived hard times ...
of various kinds...
like anyone else.
Including terminal diseases. And we saw ourselves forced to ...
take such desperate action to leave something for our families.
To leave something to our loved ones.
Excuse me. excuse me.
I, for example, suffer from a degenerative disease called Herbert's myopathy.
The police knew about it ...
and have not scruples to spread lies about me.
I'd like to tell him something. I can also be a thief ...
I have always been, I have robbed banks, robbed jewelers ...
and cleaned up villas, but I've never sold anyone.
I've never sold a woman.
I'm not an exploiter ...
who traffics ...
and violent minors, I'm not like that.
Ask the police out there that they have evidence against me.
Are you saying that the police lied to the public?
The police mind.
Mind to public opinion,
he lied to my friends,
has defamed the name of my family.
I'm a thief.
But I have the right, like everyone, not to be defamed.
I have the same direct as any other person ...
to die in peace.
And with dignity.
I can not continue, enough. Please stop.
That morning there was no talk of anything else in the world.
People were speechless in bars and taxis.
Fonollosa claims that the police lie ...
that the Ministry of the Interior would be polluting the news about its past.
And challenge them to show proof.
We were Cameroon playing against Brazil without shoes.
And everyone was rooting for us.
They ask us the line from the news. Cristina Saavedra, to you the line.
Last time: Deputy Inspector Ángel Rubio could come out of the coma.
He was in a pharmacological coma after a car accident.
Recall that the deputy inspector had an accident on the M-506.
His car crashed into a prefabricated shed in one of the lanes ...
and turned over several times.
Teacher...
did you see us on television?
Nairobi, I want you to row in unison like a rowing crew, clear?
You must tell Rio ...
that as a captain of the ship, I will take out Tokyo of prison, whatever the cost.
Now yes that I recognize my Professor!
Pass me Berlin.
Berlin.
Me?
Yes you.
Thank you.
"Yeah!
The deputy inspector Rubio is about to leave the coma.
How many chances are it true?
I don't know.
It's a naive find of the police.
They say the victim leaves the coma and you go to the hospital to finish it.
It does not even work in afternoon dramas.
And if it were not so?
It is the only one who knows who I am, the only outstanding issue.
In which room is he hospitalized?
In 119.
It's a trap.
Yes.
It's a 90% trap.
99%.
To the
- But do we want to leave that 1% to chance? -  No.
No, you'll have to go there to see if it's really a trap. And if it is not ...
you will have to do it out.
Enter a hospital ...
where there will probably be at least 50 policemen waiting for me.
Come on, Sergio, think, fuck!
You spent half your childhood in a hospital.
There must be a way to end up in a trap without getting caught,
knowing that there is the cavalry waiting for you.
The solution...
is to unseat ...
the cavalry.
A moment of attention, please.
So,
as you know, we released the hostages who chose freedom,
so here nobody was deceived ...
we kept our promise.
The promise, a couple of balls.
And, in the same way, I swear to you that the million ...
the million will be delivered to the addresses you have provided.
Lies and more lies.
We will also keep this promise, you have my word.
Attention, to all units!
Identify whoever enters.
Roger that.
Excuse me, you!
A clown has entered.
He could be masked.
Another is entering the emergency room.
What the fuck is going on?
Others are entering.
They called me too.
Get them out of there.
From here we do not pass, out.
GAMES ROOM.
Who wants a fun crazy rabbit?
Inspector, they have posted an announcement for a nonexistent casting.
Lobo, be careful, it could be in the building.
He's about to enter the room.
What's happening, someone tell me something?
False alarm, it was not him.
Inspector, the TV interview.
As verified by this network, there are no open proceedings against Fonollosa ...
for trafficking in women, exploitation of prostitution or pedophilia.
According to some sources, indiscretion could be part of a dirty game ...
orchestrated by the authorities ...
ANDRES DE FOLLENOSA ENSURES THAT THE POLICE IS MENTING
to reduce the popularity of the robbers.
This last hour, as well as the death of one of the kidnappers ...
has produced a growth in their popularity among citizens.
Me neither.
Leave.
Listen to me.
As soon as Helsinki leaves, we move, okay?
Are you sure it's time?
Mónica, I have a gun, while he has one to save.
What do you think can go wrong?
Or you tell her or I'll tell her.
I'll tell him.
The Professor will try to free Tokyo.
Where are you going?
Whore.
Where the fuck are you going?
What's wrong, is it recreation? Come on, everyone seated.
And it's the same for you, phenomenon, it's a bad day.
You know what? I really want to smash someone's nose.
And yours attracts me a lot, you know how it is.
Well, why do not you try my gun, let's see if you calm down?
Arturo.
Arturito.
You have a toy gun and I have my balls turned. What are you doing?
Toy?
No
Fuck, I do not think so.
Why do not we verify it?
This time I give you three seconds, damn bitch.
- These are two ... - Three ...
Two
One
Surprise.
Rio, smile a little.
Because...
we can go back to being a family.
Turn around.
I said to turn around.
Son of a bitch.
Come on. Quick, move.
They'll run.
- Who? - Hostages.
Come on, come on, we do not have the whole day. Mónica, open the door.
Mónica, do not listen to him, he's taking advantage of you.
Do not open the door!
You shut up, or you get a shot, phenomenon.
Do not listen to him, open the door and we'll leave from here.
SAFETY SYSTEM: DOOR IN BLOCK.
Power.
What happens?
- Does not open. - Fuck.
These motherfuckers have locked the door, fuck!
It was me.
- Back! - Arturo, throw the gun.
Throw the gun.
Arturito ...
I know that you really like cinema, but this film is getting away from you a little bit.
Not another step or I shoot him.
I probably will not leave alive, but this one will never laugh again.
Berlin, Berlin, calm.
Open the door!
Okay, okay.
Quiet.
Let's talk about it from civilians.
Leave him...
and if you want to go out, I'll help you.
Open the door for me now.
We do not open any doors.
Do you really think that?
Look, I count up to five and then I shoot him.
I have nothing to lose and I do not give a shit about anything.
So the choice is yours.
Five...
fo
Three...
Two
One
But how did he find out?
He had a remote controlled GoPro.
Piece of shit.
We are trying to trace the signal.
It's useless, it's too late now.
They screwed us again.
What is clear is that you were right,
that son of a bitch tried to get rid of Ángel.
So Ángel will have been very close to the subject to get the evidence
It is possible that they found themselves face to face.
You will forgive me but ...
I'm exhausted.
Leave a message after the beep ...
Save, I'm Raquel ...
Nothing, I'm going to get a coffee at the Hanoi ...
I'll tell you if I wanted to join you.
It would do me good to talk.
Antonio.
Keep me, they left me an envelope for her.
Who?
I do not know, it was in the pocket when we opened. What do I bring you?
A beer.
How was your day?
Well, I think it's fine.
No
It was horrible.
I organized an operation to leave with you tomorrow ...
towards these beaches, but ...
it was a disaster.
- What do I bring you? - The same.
Raquel ...
sooner or later all this will end.
So, you and I will meet at the beach.
But you have to choose a place.
Okay, okay. I did not have time.
Let's see ...
What do you think about choosing it together?
I say it's a great idea.
- Choose one ... - What a responsibility. Let's see ...
Palawan.
Let me see.
Wonderful.
But where?
Palawan, yes. It is an island in the Philippines.
It is located south-east of the archipelago, it is a little higher up ...
of the island of Borneo. It has 849 thousand inhabitants, more or less and ...
the capital is Puerto Princesa.
Ángel will have been very close to the subject to get the proof.
It is possible that they found themselves face to face.
Did you check it?
Because I do. Did you do your fucking job?
The best beaches of thin sand ...
of all the tropics.
Do not you like the Philippines?
In the next episode ...
It's a wonderful moment.
Standing.
You will work until your hands bleed.
I want you to arm the streets, ports and airports.
Take off your clothes.
This for not having killed when it was necessary.
Turn around.
Do not lie to me, I would understand it.
Who do you think stole your gun?
You do not understand it.
What should I do to make myself respected?
What should I do?
What have you done? What the fuck did you do?
It was either she or us.
Attention, we activate the "Cage" operation.
To the ground. All on the ground!
- Shoot the lens! - What the fuck is going on? Power!