Translated by the community of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
THE EVENTS AND THE SCENES TO BE FOLLOWED ARE THE FANTASY PRODUCT.
Inspector, we found the farm.
The one who helped them was here,  less than 30 hours ago.
-  He called Alberto. - That they wanted to wipe out
they would burn it in.
And I in Madrid was going. I would take the bus.
Get out of the car.
Old story!
You are being taken  for an attack on the Authority.
I get from the Department. They arrested me.
I do not know how he was hurt so I did not touch him.
-  Take his handcuffs. - What are you gonna do to me?
Real!
Who is the Professor? Very well. Take it!
Sergio! The Professor is called Sergio Marcina.
I will ask for imprisonment without suspension and communication.
Let's go.
I chop the cider in a few days and we leave for the Caribbean.
Look at her. It is beautiful and elegant.
- She is a woman of another class. - I understood!
I'm a shit and I have to dream like a shit.
You have a syndrome. Of Stockholm.
You keep on your way, I am my own and all right.
Inspector Rubio will come out of the coma.
- He's the only one who knows me. - You have to go see if it's a trap
- if not, kill him. - We'll lay on this bastard
red carpet to the bed of nell.  There will be Lobo waiting for him.
It's very difficult to escape.
In that office they keep the bag with the fake weapons.
- Who's going to get the gun? -  Monica.
While she is being treated.
Where the hell are you going?
You have a gun and I can not stand it.
Why do not we try it out?
Go on the other.
Come on, fast! Monica, open the door!
I will count as five, and then I will drop it.
Monica, do not open the door!
Rachel
this, sooner or later, will end.
And then, we both will be on the beach.
But you have to choose a place.
Good. I did not get to see. Well
What do you think we both chose together?
It looks perfect to me.
- Choose one. - Big responsibility! Well
Palawan.
To see.
Wonderful.
Where is;
Palawan is an island of the Philippines.
It is located northwest of the Archipelago
just above the Borneo Island.
It has about 849,000 inhabitants
and the capital is Puerto Princesa.
O'Nchel approached him enough if he had proof.
They may have come face to face.
You searched for him? I did it! Did you do your job?
Better beaches with fine sand
across the Tropic.
Do not you like the Philippines?
Yes
Of course!
Does it hurt to take a moment on the toilet?
Not at all.
Suarett?
A question.
What color was the clown's wig talking with the kid in the hospital?
- Was it red? -  Yes.
- For sure; -  Yes.
To make your life pieces, it's the same if you're in a toilet
Three two
one!
in a robbery
or at the entrance of the prison.
You see
That evening, the mishaps of three women would be synchronized.
Rachel suddenly understood that she had fallen in love with the balls
the greatest robber of Spain.
It's theirs.
It's with them, you've seen it all! It's with them!
Monica Gustanblue understood that he had just become a bandit accomplices
and that there was no return.
And me
I walked following the instructions given to us by the Professor.
But without any certainty
as if it were swollen.
Like a bottle that flew into the sea
without knowing if it will be picked up on the opposite bank.
If they catch you
at 24 hours of arrest, you will say you want to make an agreement.
That you want to file, but an Investigator.
They will have no other solution than to go to the Supreme Court.
And it is likely during your transfer
to be able to do something for you.
That's where I was going,
To the Court.
In the hope that my guardian angel would know the route of the vehicle
and it would save me a second life.
It was hard to have hopes on a van
guarded and handcuffed.
But it would be worse if i knew that at the same time
20 km from
my guardian angel had just been discovered.
THE PAPER HOUSE
TUESDAY 16:35
102 HOURS FROM THE PRINCIPLE
Rachel?
Alberto
have you analyzed the evidence you found in the Toledo fireplace?
Yes, but nothing positive.
What's a good thing?
They were the remains of a recent sports newspaper.
Or the data is falsified
or the guy reads sports on Sundays.
I do.
'k
how exactly did the fight with Salvah?
Damn, Rachel
I told you it was not a fight.
He grabbed me from the neck, made a grip and I fainted. I did not touch him.
It's ninja with glasses.
Why are you asking me;
Nothing.
And you say that he caused you.
Yes. He told me that I share my intelligence with my penis
and something such wise, among others.
He wanted a fight, but why?
I do not know.
Goodbye.
Alberto?
Do not touch the trays. They are sealed up again.
Take the imprints and compare them with the nell's tsp.
- You 're kidding me. - No.
Then go to my car and take fingerprints from the passenger's door.
- But do it.
We're looking for a guy
middle age with beard and glasses.
You!
You! See who he is and what he does here.
It was him.
And of course it was he.
- Do you have a charger? - No.
Do you want to get from mine?
He was from the beginning.
Always polite
always with the smile
and always in the right place.
The only citizen who had entered the scene.
I think something is happening to your daughter.
The stranger who managed to overcome all her defenses one by one.
And not just as a police officer.
Salvation
I have not
such a wonderful gift as yours
but I will improvise a surprise
in female toilets.
You will go first and then I will come.
Rachel
the time is not right and here they know us.
Salvation?
It's the first time I do not wear a parachute
and I will fall into the pool.
Do not tell me he has no water.
And of course it does.
Of course he has.
Well
go and wait with you there.
Hands on the wall!
- Rachel, what it is - Hands on the wall!
What are you doing;
- Weapons? - Do I arrest? Rachel, please.
Go round.
- Put them on. - Rachel, I guess you're joking, eh?
Wear them!
You are involved in synergy with hostage robbery at the National Mint.
-  You see  - You are right
-  eventually, third and drugged.  - Do not talk
and get to the Investigator.
And in this case he had more than suspicions.
He was bitter
had anger
was disappointed.
And Helsinki felt something similar.
Not from a spoof, but from a lack of sleep.
He had slept four hours in the last five days.
Do you know what a man does when he does not sleep?
Neural synapses are short-circuiting.
It stops secreting dopamine, ceases to metabolize glucose
and the only information in the brain is survival.
Only you can not ask someone who has five days without care
is patience.
Let's go!
Take your clothes off.
And the blouse.
- I have a wound on my shoulder - Take off your blouse!
You steal from above.
That's because you did not kill when you had to.
What will you do;
If I drop you
you will just die. You will not suffer.
Now you'll carry two pounds of explosives stuck on you
without knowing when to fire them.
Helsinki, are new explosives. Be careful, my friend.
This worm is worse than the cops.
Because of his death Oslo.
Because Denver is about to die.
That's it
the problems are over.
So, Arturite?
If you pull out the cable
it will explode.
Do not make quick moves
do not sweat
do not touch yourself.
The detonator.
If I push
this button
Nor will your wife recognize it
the pieces of Arturite.
Do you have a cigarette?
- Do you have a cigarette? - You are pregnant.
Pregnant, hostage, shot
and over and over accuse me of synergy in an armed spiral
Do not think the worst.
Arturo will help you, he is your child's father.
Who father?
Who "gave" me as a common kidnapper?
Where did I open my head with an iron pole?
Most likely my companions will help me.
Besides, I just broke down their escape plan.
They'll set me up at three meters, of course. How stupid I am when I got fucked up!
Come on, give me a cigarette. I want an ass-cigarette!
They will not sit in the stool, because, I swear to you, I will crush them all.
- You will not crush anyone, calm down! - She's right, she got them on her throat!
Whether we break it or stay and catch us, it will go to jail.
He has painted her, anyway.
Fuck!
I always make the wrong choices.
I choose a married man
start a baby
then another comes
shoots me on the foot
and I go
and I fall in love with him.
Do you know what we're gonna do?
- What; - Will you come with us.
After crossing the line, it's over. I will not leave you alone.
- My child, he can - He will come with us.
It will take the position of Tokyo or Oslo and finally.
No, listen.
I am a simple secretary.
I do not think I can get it out of the Police, shoot it
to live hidden, who knows where, in Cambodia
or any other country.
Better to stay.
And when the police arrive, I'll tell them
that I did because I had the Stockholm Syndrome.
This scenario has some attenuators
while the other, no.
"Stockholm".
What;
Sounds beautiful.
If you come with us
I could call you 'Stockholm'.
I do not know, man.
Get out.
It's gone.
Go in.
We were all exhausted.
From insomnia
anxiety
and the anguish to carry a secret a year
in that strangling environment, it was getting harder to keep it.
And all, sooner or later
We lost the ball.
Except Berlin.
He was the only one to apply restlessly the protocol of rest.
The rest
was upset.
I tried to be good.
I tried to give you what they promised you.
Let me get rid of you from Berlin.
Make all of this meaningful.
After all that I've lost here, it makes sense.
I am a good person.
I was good.
And the world
it spits me down.
I tried to give you oxygen
and you brought it back to me.
Berlin;
Berlin.
He spent over an hour and a half.
You did not want to kill me
while I was asleep?
Not even a little;
You laugh.
That means I'm not afraid anymore.
Let's say the anxiolytics I get have neutralized me.
If everything goes well
which is unlikely, if I do not think of reins
but
in case they go
I want to offer you a deal.
A romantic collaboration.
In a few days, I'll send you an air ticket.
For a very distant place.
If you want
you can come with me.
Very little time
many desires.
And after
after my end
everything I have will belong to you.
It would be really wonderful
to love me a lot.
Nevertheless
I do not live with expectations
with hallucinations.
I have many defects
and I know it.
I can stand
to become my partner
on the last trip.
You and me together
until the end.
You do not understand.
What do I have to do to respect you?
What should I do;
Cut an ear
and send it to your father?
Or throw you on your leg and never again rejoice?
Great idea!
It is time to become practical.
The utopia of cooperation
failed
Nairobi.
Thank you for letting me
to rest a little of my obligations.
But we are all prepared
to return to headquarters.
All yours.
It's a wonderful time!
Stand up!
I told you
that I would protect you, right?
But I changed my mind.
It is much more practical
to torture you.
In concentration camps
respect is taken for granted.
It will be the same here.
You will dig the tunnel
until your hands are bleeding!
At nights you can cry out of terror in your rack
but then, you will continue to dig!
You will do your job without a break
otherwise, an epic punishment is waiting for you.
Like your leader.
A guy who, if he reborn, will kill.
If he again has a passion for freedom, he will kill!
Where to sweat a lot
will kill.
A man with an explosive character.
Now you will be afraid of them, Arturo.
Though we always knew you were doing it.
Since you are still, you will stay here separately.
Helsinki, the rest in the tunnel!
Go ahead, go!
Quickly!
Seismographs have detected unusual activity
in the submountain of the Mint. Probably the robbers increased
the pace of digging tunnels. They are ready to open it.
- How long does it stay? - Two meters, according to the geodatar.
- Two and a half. - Where will they end up?
We believe here.
In a collector about 15 meters behind the building.
Attention all! Be ready. Notify them to the ground.
I want 20 men to keep the collector.
Do you know what the guilty people are doing when they go to the crime scene?
They do not stop talking.
For the time being, for politics
they say jokes
from anxiety.
Because they can not stand the silence.
But you
you do not say anything.
What do you mean, Rachel?
Who you are;
Sergio Marcina.
Sergio?
Salvation?
The professor;
The one who made a chess mat
the Police, the National Intelligence Center and the Special Bodies?
The man I was talking to on the phone for five days?
I told him
what clothes I wore, and what kind of orgasms I had.
Which of them are you?
Why are not your footprints in the National Database?
I had to renew my identity before digitizing them.
When did you get it?
It's been over 20 years.
That gives you plenty of possibilities, right?
Why nobody will denounce someone's disappearance
which simply does not exist.
Which means I will not even need to burn your body well.
You want this;
Kill me and burn me?
Yes.
I certify you yes.
Look
perhaps as an Inspector
I should not have said that
to the person who organized the robbery at the National Mint.
But as a woman
as a woman who spent years scaring everyone
everything
and who trusted someone
someone who knew how fragile and vulnerable they were
and yet she was beating her from the beginning, from the first moment
I do not think it is so absurd, right?
You could
to have approached me
to fish me
give me a microphone, fuck me!
But no. Slowly!
Yesterday we had dreams together.
Fuck!
We were talking about the future. For the future!
Who the hell are you?
What are you; An old-timer?
It was all designed, Rachel.
All. Everything.
I'm so sorry. It was all designed
except what happened between us.
- I do not know, it missed me. - What;
- I did not calculate this variable. - What the hell are you saying?
- What variable? - To fall in love with you.
Seriously, I think I'll let you continue the same violin
old man?
That I will be stingy while you are mocking me
- like I'm fifteen years old? - I'm not lying to you, Rachel.
I've fallen in love with you.
Tell me again. Come on again. Dare to get it back.
Rachel
I've fallen in love with you.
I'm so sorry.
Very well.
17:46 THE TIME
Berlin, I want to talk to you.
Of course. I am again a leader.
I need food for my puppies.
What the Professor said exactly to you
for Tokyo?
He told me he would try to free her.
And how will he release it on his own?
Rio
he will not do it.
Who, then?
The four Serbs who finished the tunnel five years ago.
It's "wild" for extreme cases.
- When will it be done; - I do not know.
You feel her absence, right?
For those who stay behind is harder.
She, on the contrary, will expand
her experiences
satisfying her wishes
will have fun.
Would you like to accept the deal with the Police?
Completely.
What if we walked out of here?
Would we go on together?
- You mean to betray your friends. - My friends with city names?
Tokyo, Berlin, Moscow, Denver.
My friends with city names look great to me.
And I'll tell you something.
Look at hiding if you accept the deal.
Because if I see you, I'll throw you in the temple.
Women always turn the page first. Look at being prepared.
Tokyo is impulsive
but he will turn
and we will be together.
I know.
Of course!
For sure.
I have always believed the same thing.
If you betray us and you leave
and you want to take me when you regret
because you believe me
you will regret this
you can call your cell phone.
I will have it open.
The police will hear us, but it will not matter anymore.
ALISSON PARKER
Suarett, she opened her cell phone Lisin Parker.
- Try to hurt it. - The camera is covered.
They do not call or send anything.
What the fuck is going on? My horn!
A prisoner transport unit here!  We are attacking!
Here Centrally. I do not get you clean. Repeat, please.
- We have interference. - My horn inside!
My guardian angel had not forsaken me.
And I felt like I was in the train of horror.
It's a bomb!
- What's going on in there? - They've put us in a bomb!
In a dark tunnel where you do not know where the skeleton will be thrown away.
- We're losers! - Shut up!
But how fun!
What happened; What the fuck is going on?
- Damn, they're killing us! - Stop!
- We're losers! - Shut up! I'm trying to think!
Outside!
OK OK! Non!
Download the weapons, otherwise I shoot.
If you shoot a girl, you are dying.
If you shoot me
you are dying.
If you leave a girl, you live.
I wish all the decisions in the world were so easy.
Right?
Rio.
Rio!
Before, I realized that you did not agree with what Helsinki did.
You are not like them.
You are a good guy.
You know, I have a son in your age.
The big one.
And he's a good kid.
Help me please.
I want to see my son.
I found the passport machine.
- No no. - Monica.
'fuck me.
You can do whatever you want.
But, if you change your mind?
I thought it would be good to have a new one.
- That's good stuff. - I know it, I work here.
- You'll like it, let's do it. - No.
If you do not want it, go for it, burn it, whatever you want.
Two minutes will take us only.
- We do it; - Yes, okay.
- Did you connect it? - Yeah.
Okay.
What name should I put?
- '' fuck ''. - '' gatha '';
- What's up; - Sounds like a porn star.
The "gatha" is very beautiful.
If you were ugly, I would tell you to put "Fenissa" or "Marie-Krouth".
- "Maria Fernandez." - "Maria Fernandez"?
Very trivial. You will not believe it. 'oh me, I know of them.
- It's more discreet. - '' Ghatah '' sounds a trifle.
Put it on.
- Here you go. - Thanks.
He was born in Madrid
and the date you want.
- We're making a passport. - Indeed.
Did he eventually pop it?
or come with us.
Who do you think he got your gun?
Come outside.
Suareth.
I invite you from the Supreme Court.
The conveyor that carried Silene Oliveira
had to be here for 15 minutes and has not arrived. We have no news.
Keep me up to date.
Gomet?
Two units to make Oliveira's route to the court.
They have not arrived yet. I want to know what's running.
Understandable.
Wear it.
Unique Contact Professor.
That's what you're doing.
I had never felt so free.
But that time, the Professor's plan would not work.
I know that pressure has come from me.
That I was wrong
but, please
I do not deserve that.
Please
I am asking you
if you have a little dignity.
I can not breathe.
I can not breathe, help me.
Help me please.
We are entering
we get food and we sit.
One measure from each other. Come on, let's go!
That's what it is.
In a row. Helsinki
say hello to Arturite. Aruritus?
There is something that does not make sense.
Before they said that if I was going to be shaking in the air
but they have me here.
With this unbearable heat. It makes a terrible heat!
It is best to be calm and silent.
- It does not make sense. - What thing;
The bomb has no logic.
You think she would risk sweating it
and to shake the whole pattern in the air?
No. It would be madness.
- They do not work like this. - Stuck!
They're making a psychological war, you do not understand?
They are trying to terrify us. This is fake, a bluff.
I do not know and do not want to know. So you smell!
I'll take it out, I decided. I'll get it out, I can not do more.
There will be nothing. If it was to explode, they would not have put us all together.
- Stay calm and sit down. - Who are you
what will you tell us what to do?
Especially you, because we are locked in here!
- Because of me; - Yeah, because of you.
You are Director here
and eight madmen came in as if they were home.
Is there another Mint in the world who robbed you?
Only that, right?
Congratulations.
You wrote a story.
Now, please, do not let it blow in the air
and sit down!
Have a seat!
Center, are you receiving me? The van was hit.
-  No trace of Oliveira.  - Received. Wait for instructions.
Caution! We have one fugitive.
We are activating the Cage business!
It was not there.
It was not.
It had organized them all.
He had sent to save me.
How could it not be there?
That afternoon of October, they applied for my flight
the Cage business. It happens when there are attacks.
The police "cut off" all the city's exits.
Everything paralyzes and you are trapped.
You can only hide.
The problem was that the hiding place was the warehouse
And the one who would open me was the Professor.
And I've never done it well with the wait.
What is that?
The only truth I know about you is that you are a professional liar.
Tell me paranoid, but you will not lie to me again.
I assure you.
Do you think I do not know? That I'm a mole?
Of course, he took that weapon.
She regretted it, but if not, I would now be with Oslo.
Okay, hello, let's get it right.
But do not make a passport and get it.
And if I want that?
And if I want to live with her and take her child?
You have enough of your own problems to take over the other.
She is a girl who loves me and her child is not to blame.
- You do not have to get involved. - I mean, because I want it.
It's times we're going to help somebody, but we're diving first.
If I swim, I swim as I did a lifetime.
It's not that simple, damn it! He has lived firsthand.
All my life I was trying to help your mother.
Where does this hang now?
Mom left us.
What does this mean now?
We abandoned it.
Why would he pull us into the abyss.
I put her in a clinic in Barcelona.
It cost me 200,000 pesetas.
And within 24 hours he came to my pension
- badly made with heroin. - What did you do;
It was the fourth time
- I lost my savings. - What the hell did you do?
She wanted to go buy something else.
I put her in the car
and I left it in a square
near a settlement where they sold heroin.
I did not expect it.
I came to find you
To leave.
Have you left my mother in a square?
That's why I put you in this bay.
Not to live the life I've lived.
Because I want you to be free, I want you to start
A mother does not give up!
Help her get deaconated!
All my life made me think she was a bastard!
I thought he might have left because of me!
It was her or we.
I do not break your head because we need you to get out of here.
When we get out
we will be two strangers.
Two strangers.
Denver
and Moscow.
Did you even finish your passport?
Yes.
Denver, are you okay?
I put the '' goat ''.
I was driving at frenzied speed nowhere.
In a fraction of a second I knew where to go.
The bad was
that it was the most guarded part of the country.
Take a deep breath.
Do you have anxiety?
No, I am fine.
Do you see those lines?
Each lie will translate into ugly curves.
Due to a blood pressure disorder
heart rate and respiratory rate.
Do not lie to me, then, because I will know it.
Name.
Sergio Marcina.
Place of birth.
San Sebastian.
Did you know that you would destroy the nell?
Yes.
You caused his accident?
No.
Was your idea of ​​robbery in the Mint?
Who thought it?
My father.
He died before he realized it, so it's like a tribute.
The story of the damned apples.
The history of organic cider
you told me yesterday in bed
was the story of robbery.
And I was listening to you like stupid.
You were laughing at me from the beginning. From the first moment!
I did not laugh with you, Rachel. Look, please, the polygraph.
Look at him.
My father had a sick son
and not even a fivefold knocker.
What would you do;
All day he was thinking of robberies
to pay a hospital in the US.
From despair.
To save my life.
Me
because nobody
you do
he did not help him.
And in this endeavor, they threw it with bullets.
In the entrance
of a bank.
This is the reality.
I guess there are many ways to judge what's right.
Have you considered me easy prey because I was a battered woman?
Yes, I thought so.
When you leaked to the press
my refusal to release eleven hostages instead of Lisa Parker
you knew that they would publicly "lynch" me
that my career would be destroyed and that my mother, my daughter, would see it.
Yes.
I do. And
you slept with me just because I'm the head of the case, right?
- You slept with me just for this. - No no.
- Stop lying, fuck! - I am not lying to you.
Do you want to believe that you feel something about me?
I do not want you to believe anything. It's what I feel.
Not expecting
but it happened to me. The same to you.
It happened to you, otherwise, what are we doing here?
Why am I not in the detention center? What good does that mean?
I'm not crazy, Rachel. It is something that happens to both of us.
In both, do you understand? It happened to us both.
Yes, Suareth.
Inspector, Silene Oliveira escaped.
- What; -  Going to court.
He asked to file with the Investigator.  The convoy was hit
from a group of people from eastern countries. I activated the "Cage".
- I hope they have not come out of Madrid. -  Go straight to the Investigator.
To issue an international arrest warrant.
Track national roads, harbors and airports.
Get patrolled at the border.
Tokyo escaped.
You did it;
Did you get a killer from a high security prison while I'm holding you here?
I had prepared everything before we went to the café.
I'm sorry for the reception, but I just came back.
Darko, I'm so sorry for your brother.
Come in.
You've all thought about it with millimeter accuracy, right?
Rachel, I told you everything.
I came here without showing resistance.
And if I let you interrogate me
is why
I wanted to be honest with you. I can not stand this lie any longer.
Stop it.
I do not want to hurt you anymore. It is a great relief
Laugh, finally, fuck!
I have no intention of hearing you again!
'k
from now on, whatever you are saying, you will tell the Investigator directly.
Get up.
Get up, get it!
Move on.
Move on!
Keep walking.
- I'm so sorry, Rachel. - He continued
I'll shoot!
It will
Have you heard the phrase "Am I in the mouth of the wolf?"
A call is made to her cell phone.
From an unknown number. Identify it.
- Yes? - Rio?
I'm Tokyo.
-  Is Silene Oliveira.  - Write!
- Find the call! - Where are you;
Wait!  They're listening to us.
I do not care.
It's an erotic phone call.  And the police are crazy for love.
'fuck me.
Do you remember the door that my mom made me when I was afraid?
Which door is talking about?
Yes, my love,  and of course I remember it.
- What happens; - I'll pass it.
I will pass the door of the sky.
Why does my guardian angel do not appear.
One minute.
I love you.
I love you too.
What was this phone call?
It looked like farewell.
Gentlemen, be careful. Unauthorized vehicle on the perimeter.
Lets go, lets go!
- You! Stand up! - That's it!
Door
He will pass the door
Damn, the door!
You. Stand up.
Caution! It's Silene Oliveira!
Tokyo is coming!
Below! Everybody on the floor!
We have to open the door!
Shoot the target! Shoot the motorcyclist!
Let's go!
No! We have to cover it!
We have a bandit in sight.
Dad, watch!
Beware, behind you! Back to you!
Fuck!
Moscow!
THE NEXT EPISODE
You have to go out the fastest.
Andres, they've discovered me.
I do not know how much the police will do to come here.
Did you find the Inspector?
Fuck!